Communications Workers of America Audio Tape Inventory OH.026
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Communications Workers of America Audio Tape Inventory
1952-1987
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Communications Workers of America
OH.026
92 boxes
Access Restrictions
Open for research without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by the Communications Workers of America in 1995. The accession number associated with this collection is 1987.016.
Historical/Biographical Note
The Communications Workers of America (CWA) which was founded in 1947 as an industrial union of telephone industry workers expanded in the latter decades of the twentieth century to include a variety of categories of workers, among them television and radio technicians, journalists, healthcare workers, and a large and growing division of public employees. The union frequently commissioned or otherwise acquired audio recordings of major union events, speeches by union officers and others, broadcasts, and publicity and educational materials.
Scope and Content Note
The processed portion of this collection of audiotapes includes speeches and broadcasts by CWA presidents Joseph A. Beirne, Glenn E. Watts and Morton Bahr, as well as presentations by such notables as Lyndon B. Johnson, Walter Reuther, Hubert Humphrey, Arthur J. Goldberg, George Meany, John F. Kennedy, Jimmy Carter, and Walter F. Mondale. Also included are recorded sessions of CWA conventions, conferences, and Bargaining Council meetings, as well as radio broadcasts and interviews conducted on picket lines. The unprocessed portion of the collection includes a series of oral history interviews with local and national CWA officers conducted by John N. Schacht in the 1970s.
Audiovisual Access Policies and Procedures
Audiovisual materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers. Materials not yet digitized will need to have access copies made before they can be used. To request an access copy, or if you are unsure if an item has been digitized, please contact tamiment.wagner@nyu.edu with the collection name, collection number, and a description of the item(s) requested. A staff member will respond to you with further information.
Labor unions -- Political activity -- United States.; Labor unions -- Elections -- United States.; Labor unions -- Telecommunication -- United States.; Telecommunication -- Employees -- United States.; Audiocassettes.; Audiotapes.; Carter, Jimmy, 1924-; Bahr, Morton; Humphrey, Hubert H. (Hubert Horatio), 1911-1978; Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973; Goldberg, Arthur J.; Watts, Glenn E.; Meany, George, 1894-1980; Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963
- Series I: Sound Cassettes, 1952-1987
  - Preservation masters, cassettes NS26A 2-34 (Box 93)
    - CWA Convention (Morning Session): President Beirne's Opening Address, Jun 16, 1952 (Cassette NS26A-2)
    - CWA Convention: President Beirne's Closing Address, Jun 26, 1953 (Cassette NS26A-3)
    - Allan S. Haywood and Philip Murray Memorials, England and Scotland (excerpts), Oct 10-11, 1953 (Cassette NS26A-4)
    - CWA Convention: Walter Reuther's Address, Jun 22, 1954 (Cassette NS26A-5)
    - CWA Convention: Walter Reuther's Address, Jun 22, 1954 (Cassette NS26A-6)
    - District 6 Meeting: Southern Bell Strike, Dec 23, 1954 (Cassette NS26A-7)
    - CWA Reception: Harry S. Truman, Dec 23, 1954 (Cassette NS26A-8)
    - CWA Convention (Afternoon Session): President Beirne Introduces G. Meany, Jun 11, 1956 (Cassette NS26A-9)
    - CWA Convention (Evening Session): Werkau Memorial Service, Jun 14, 1956 (Cassette NS26A-10)
    - CWA Convention: President Beirne's Closing Address, Jun 15, 1956 (Cassette NS26A-11)
    - International Affairs: George Meany's Address to Hungarian Refugees, Dec 17, 1956 (Cassette NS26A-12)
    - International Affairs: Interview with Serafino Romualdi, AFL-CIO Inter-American Representative, Dec 20, 1956 (Cassette NS26A-13)
    - International Affairs: 5th Congress of ICFTU with A. Philip Randolph, 1957 (Cassette NS26A-14)
    - Strike Activities: A.T. Jones, 1957 (Cassette NS26A-15)
    - AFL-CIO Conference on Atomic Radiation Hazards: George Meany, Feb 28, 1957 (Cassette NS26A-16)
    - CWA Convention: President Beirne's Opening and Closing Addresses, Jun 17; Jun 21, 1957 (Cassette NS26A-17)
    - International Affairs: William Schnitzler's & Irving Brown's Speeches before ICFTU, Jul 19, 1957 (Cassette NS26A-18)
    - Labor Probe Section: "Big News of 1957", Dec 29, 1957 (Cassette NS26A-19)
    - Radio Broadcast: WRTTP with Senator Paul Douglas & Senator Jacob Javits, Feb 7, 1958 (Cassette NS26A-20)
    - CWA Convention (Evening Session): President Beirne's Closing Address, Jun 13, 1958 (Cassette NS26A-22)
    - AFL-CIO Conference: March for Integrated Schools, Oct 22, 1958 (Cassette NS26A-23)
    - AFL-CIO Conference: Youth March for Integrated Schools with Coretta Scott King, Oct 22, 1958 (Cassette NS26A-24)
    - Interview with President Beirne: Transmitting on Armed Forces Radio Station, Nov 14, 1958 (Cassette NS26A-25)
    - JAB Interview: 'How Latin Americans See Us', Nov 14, 1958 (Cassette NS26A-26)
    - Senator Goldwater on Taft-Hartley & Steel Strike, Nov 14, 1958 (Cassette NS26A-27)
    - U.S.-Canadian Conference Program of Education Directors: Peter Schoemann, Joe Glazer, Jan 14, 1959 (Cassette NS26A-28)
    - Senate Sub-Committee on Labor: Senators J.F. Kennedy, Morse, Goldwater, Randolph, Beimiller, Jan 28, 1959 (Cassette NS26A-29)
    - Senate Sub-Committee on Labor: Senators J.F. Kennedy, Morse, Goldwater, Randolph, Beimiller, Jan 28, 1959 (Cassette NS26A-30)
    - Senate Sub-Committee: Senators J.F. Kennedy, Morse, Goldwater, Beimiller, Jan 28, 1959 (Cassette NS26A-31)
    - Voice of America: Interview with President Beirne, Feb 4, 1959 (Cassette NS26A-32)
    - AFL-CIO 5th National Legislative Conference: Senator J.F. Kennedy & Senator R.J. Grey, Mar 2, 1959 (Cassette NS26A-33)
    - AFL-CIO Conference on Unemployment: Harry Van Arsdale, Jr., George Meany, G. Harrison, Apr 8, 1959 (Cassette NS26A-34)
  - Preservation masters, cassettes NS26A 35-68 (Box 94)
    - AFL-CIO Conference on Unemployment: George Meany, Walter Reuther, Apr 8, 1959 (Cassette NS26A-35)
    - AFL-CIO Conference on Unemployment: Senator Lyndon B. Johnson, Apr 8, 1959 (Cassette NS26A-36)
    - Labor Rallies: Detroit's Africa Freedom Rally with Walter Reuther & Tom Mboya, Apr 23, 1959 (Cassette NS26A-37)
    - Labor Rallies: Detroit's Africa Freedom Rally with Tom Mboya, Apr 23, 1959 (Cassette NS26A-38)
    - Senate Labor Committee on Minimum Wage: Senator Goldwater; Msgr. George Higgins, May 8, 1959 (Cassette NS26A-39)
    - Radio Broadcasts: Hubert Humphrey, Stuart Udall, Thompson, Senator Douglas, Aug 7, 1959 (Cassette NS26A-40)
    - AFL-CIO Convention: Arthur J. Goldberg's Address, U.S. Steel Workers, Nov 9, 1959 (Cassette NS26A-41)
    - AFL-CIO IUD Convention: Walter Reuther, Nov 9, 1959 (Cassette NS26A-42)
    - Strike Activities: Glenn E. Watts Interviews Walkout, May 13, 1905 (Cassette NS26A-43)
    - Radio Broadcasts: Jay Lovestone (Summit Failure- KMOX), May 27, 1960 (Cassette NS26A-44)
    - International Affairs: Maida Springer Speaks to Workers of British Guiana, Jun 16, 1960 (Cassette NS26A-45)
    - Jay Lovestone Interview by August Soetebier, Oct 14, 1960 (Cassette NS26A-46)
    - Radio Broadcasts: WRTTP with President Kennedy, Representative Clement Zablocki, Representative Walter Judd, May 14, 1960 (Cassette NS26A-47)
    - Radio Broadcasts: As We See It with Boris Shishkin & Don Slaiman, Jan 1, 1961 (Cassette NS26A-48)
    - Radio Broadcasts: As We See It with Senator Hubert Humphrey, Don Slaiman, Mrs. John McFerrin, Feb 12, 1961 (Cassette NS26A-49)
    - Strike Activities: IBEW/Upstate NY, Mar 1, 1961 (Cassette NS26A-50)
    - 13th Annual Roosevelt Day Dinner: Walter Reuther, Willy Brandt, Joe Raugh, Mar 13, 1961 (Cassette NS26A-51)
    - Radio Broadcasts: JAB Labor News Conference, May 21, 1961 (Cassette NS26A-52)
    - Radio Broadcasts: As We See It with JAB, Senator Hubert Humphrey, H. Pollock, C.J. Haggerty, May 28, 1961 (Cassette NS26A-53)
    - AFL-CIO All American Conference to Combat Communism: Jay Lovestone & Dr. G. Ford, Nov 4, 1961 (Cassette NS26A-54)
    - International Affairs: Opening of Friendship Office, AFL-CIO/NYC Central Labor Council with Harry Van Arsdale, Jr. & George Meany, 1962 (Cassette NS26A-55)
    - CWA Convention: President Kennedy's Taped Remarks, Jun 5, 1963 (Cassette NS26A-56)
    - Telstar Message: Joseph A. Beirne, CWA 25th Anniversary Message, Jun 10, 1963 (Cassette NS26A-56)
    - CWA Convention (Morning-Afternoon Sessions): Resolutions; Britain; Bargaining Comm.; Ron Smith, Postal Workers; Harding, Civil Rights, Jun 13, 1963 (Cassette NS26A-57)
    - CWA 25th Anniversary Banquet, Jun 14, 1963 (Cassette NS26A-59)
    - CWA 25th Anniversary Banquet: Walter Reuther's Speech, Jun 14, 1963 (Cassette NS26A-60)
    - CWA Convention (Morning Session): Foreign Policy; Appeals Comm.; President Beirne's Closing Remarks, Jun 13-14, 1963 (Cassette NS26A-61)
    - Radio Broadcasts: As We See It with President Beirne, Oct 20, 1963 (Cassette NS26A-62)
    - Radio Broadcasts: As We See It with President Beirne, Oct 20, 1963 (Cassette NS26A-63)
    - Radio Broadcasts: Representative Cecil King Interview, Nov 21, 1963 (Cassette NS26A-64)
    - JAB's Speech to Local 1101 Stewards, NY, Jan 22, 1964 (Cassette NS26A-65)
    - District 1 Meeting: NY Raid- Teamsters, Jan 28, 1964 (Cassette NS26A-66)
    - District 1 Meeting: NY Raid- Teamsters, Jan 28, 1964 (Cassette NS26A-67)
    - Radio Broadcasts: JAB on Barry Grey Radio Show, Jan 29, 1964 (Cassette NS26A-68)
  - Preservation masters, cassettes NS26A 69-70, 73-96, 100-108 (Box 95)
    - Radio Broadcasts: WRTTP with Senator Hubert Humphrey & Senator Jacob Javits, Feb 9, 1964 (Cassette NS26A-69)
    - Radio Broadcasts: As We See It with Michael Harrington, Mar 8, 1964 (Cassette NS26A-70)
    - Radio Broadcasts: As We See It with Senator Hubert Humphrey at Four Freedoms Dinner, Apr 26, 1964 (Cassette NS26A-73)
    - CWA Convention (Morning Session): President Johnson's Address, Jun 17, 1964 (Cassette NS26A-74)
    - Radio Broadcasts: As We See It with President Johnson, Jun 21, 1964 (Cassette NS26A-75)
    - Radio Broadcasts: WRTTP with President Johnson, Esther Peterson, Aug 9, 1964 (Cassette NS26A-76)
    - Radio Broadcasts: WRTTP with Senator Al Gore & Senator Clifford Case, Sep 20, 1964 (Cassette NS26A-77)
    - Radio Broadcasts: As We See It with Esther Peterson, Nov 8, 1964 (Cassette NS26A-78)
    - CWA Convention: President Lyndon B. Johnson, Jun 1, 1965 (Cassette NS26A-79)
    - Civil Rights Hearing, Washington, DC: Otis Matthews, UAW, Feb 18, 1965 (Cassette NS26A-80)
    - Civil Rights Hearing, Washington, DC, Feb 18, 1965 (Cassette NS26A-81)
    - Radio Broadcasts: As We See It with President Lyndon B. Johnson & JAB, Feb 28, 1965 (Cassette NS26A-82)
    - Radio Broadcasts: As We See It with Gus Tyler, ILGWU, Mar 7, 1965 (Cassette NS26A-83)
    - Radio Broadcasts: As We See It with President Lyndon B. Johnson, George Meany, President Beirne, Edgar F. Kaiser, May 30, 1965 (Cassette NS26A-84)
    - Press Conference USA: JAB on Automation, Sep 4, 1965 (Cassette NS26A-85)
    - Murray-Green Award Dinner: JAB, Mrs. Eunice Kennedy Shriver, Leo Perlis, May 19, 1966 (Cassette NS26A-86)
    - Strike Activities: NYC Picket Line Interviews, 1968 (Cassette NS26A-87)
    - Strike Activities: Local Rally Speeches; Down-State NY; Picket Line Interviews, 1968 (Cassette NS26A-88)
    - Strike Activities: J. Ratti Tapes, Local 2590 (Anti-CWA Tapes), 1968 (Cassette NS26A-89)
    - Headquarters Meeting (Afternoon Session): President Beirne, Glenn Watts, Gus Cramer, 1968 (Cassette NS26A-90)
    - Strike Activities: Picket Line Interviews; Operators; Plantmen- Western Electric Installers, Apr 18, 1968 (Cassette NS26A-91)
    - Strike Activities: NYC Rally (Bell System Strike), Apr 25, 1968 (Cassette NS26A-92)
    - Strike Activities: NYC Rally (Bell System Strike), Apr 25, 1968 (Cassette NS26A-93)
    - CWA Convention: President Beirne's Opening & Closing Addresses, Jun 17; Jun 21, 1968 (Cassette NS26A-94)
    - History of CWA: President Beirne, Nov 13, 1968 (Cassette NS26A-95)
    - William Smallwood Testimonial Dinner: President Beirne & Glenn Watts, Mar 31, 1969 (Cassette NS26A-96)
    - CWA Special Convention: Opening Address, Mar 22, 1971 (Cassette NS26A-100)
    - CWA Special Convention: Closing Address, Mar 24, 1971 (Cassette NS26A-101)
    - Radio Broadcasts: "CWA Membership Meeting of the Air" with President Beirne & Glenn Watts, May 23, 1971 (Cassette NS26A-102)
    - George McGovern Speech, Aug 25, 1972 (Cassette NS26A-103)
    - Joseph A. Beirne on "CWA Task Force 71", May 24, 1972 (Cassette NS26A-104)
    - AFL-CIO Jobs Conference: COPE Report, Sep 1, 1971 (Cassette NS26A-105)
    - The AFL-CIO and President Nixon, Jan 1, 1972 (Cassette NS26A-106)
    - Beirne on the Value Added Tax, Mar 1, 1972 (Cassette NS26A-107)
    - Glenn Watts on the Packwood Bill, Apr 1, 1972 (Cassette NS26A-108)
  - Preservation masters, cassettes NS26A 109-142 (Box 96)
    - Beirne at Legislative Conference, May 1, 1972 (Cassette NS26A-109)
    - Beirne/Filbey on the CWA-APWU Merger, Jun 1, 1972 (Cassette NS26A-110)
    - "Politics and your Contract", Aug 1, 1972 (Cassette NS26A-111)
    - Beirne on CWA Priorities for '73, Jan 1, 1973 (Cassette NS26A-112)
    - 1973 Legislative Conference (Excerpts), Apr 1, 1973 (Cassette NS26A-113)
    - President Beirne on 'Politics', May 1, 1973 (Cassette NS26A-114)
    - President Beirne on 'Politics', May 1, 1973 (Cassette NS26A-115)
    - Beirne on Organizing, Aug 1, 1973 (Cassette NS26A-116)
    - "1974: A Big Year", Sep 1, 1973 (Cassette NS26A-117)
    - CWA Flight II: Spots 9-15, 1974 (Cassette NS26A-118)
    - CWA Local Radio Network (G.E. Watts Special File on Bargaining): Side A: Introduction; Side B: Commercial Messages, 1974 (Cassette NS26A-119)
    - Bell South Bargaining Council: President Beirne Opening, Jan 16, 1974 (Cassette NS26A-120)
    - CWA Legislative-Political Highlights, Feb 1, 1974 (Cassette NS26A-121)
    - Glenn Watts' 1974 Labor Day Statement, Apr 1, 1974 (Cassette NS26A-122)
    - CWA Convention: Opening & Closing (Excerpts), Feb 1, 1975 (Cassette NS26A-123)
    - CWA Endorses Carter, Jan 1, 1976 (Cassette NS26A-124)
    - Watts on 1976 Politics, Feb 1, 1976 (Cassette NS26A-125)
    - Watts on Collective Bargaining, Mar 1, 1976 (Cassette NS26A-126)
    - Watts on Collective Bargaining, Mar 1, 1976 (Cassette NS26A-127)
    - Interview with Watts: Conclusion, Apr 1, 1976 (Cassette NS26A-128)
    - Watts' BSBC Press Conference, Jan 1, 1977 (Cassette NS26A-129)
    - Watts Announces Strike Vote, Feb 1, 1977 (Cassette NS26A-130)
    - "Unity and Spirit = Victory", Mar 1, 1977 (Cassette NS26A-131)
    - CWA Convention: Resolutions Committee; Presentation of President's Award, Jun 23, 1977 (Cassette NS26A-132)
    - CWA Convention: Trustee's Report; Andrew Young Address; Foreign Policy Statement, Jun 23, 1977 (Cassette NS26A-133)
    - CWA Convention: United Way Presentation with Beaumont; Resolutions Committee, Jun 23, 1977 (Cassette NS26A-134)
    - CWA Convention (Evening Session): Bargaining Report, Jun 23, 1977 (Cassette NS26A-135)
    - CWA Convention (Evening Session): Bargaining Report, Jun 23, 1977 (Cassette NS26A-136)
    - CWA Convention (Morning Session), Jun 24, 1977 (Cassette NS26A-137)
    - CWA Convention (Morning Session), Jun 24, 1977 (Cassette NS26A-138)
    - CWA Convention (Afternoon Session): Adjournment, Jun 24, 1977 (Cassette NS26A-139)
    - CWA Press Conference: Watts on Imminent Strike, Aug 4, 1977 (Cassette NS26A-140)
    - Interview with Glenn Watts, Part 1, Aug 9, 1977 (Cassette NS26A-141)
    - Interview with Glenn Watts, Part 2, Aug 9, 1977 (Cassette NS26A-142)
  - Preservation masters, cassettes NS26A 143-176 (Box 97)
    - Alabama State Meeting: President Watts, Sep 18, 1977 (Cassette NS26A-143)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: Monday R-1; Side B: Monday R-2, Watts, Part 1, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-144)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: Monday #3: Watts; Side B: Monday #4, Watts, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-145)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: Monday R-7; Side B: Monday R-8, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-146)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: Monday R-9; Side B: Monday R-10, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-147)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: Monday Evening R-11; Side B: Monday Evening R-12, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-148)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: Mon-Tues R-13; Side B: R-14, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-149)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: Tuesday R-15; Side B: Tuesday R-16, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-150)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: R-17; Side B: R-18, Roll Call, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-151)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: R-18A, Roll Call; Side B: R-19, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-152)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: 19A; Side B: 20, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-153)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: 20A; Side B: 21, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-154)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: R-21A; Side B: R-22, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-155)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: R-22; Side B: R-23, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-156)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: 24; Side B: 25, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-157)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: 26; Side B: 27, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-158)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: 28; Side B: 29, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-159)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: 29A; Side B: 30, Cope Awards, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-160)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: 31; Side B: 32, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-161)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: 33; Side B: 34, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-162)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: 35; Side B: 36, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-163)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: 39; Side B: 40, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-164)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: 41; Side B: 42, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-165)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: 43; Side B: 44, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-166)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: 45; Side B: 46, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-167)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: 47, President Watts Close; Side B: 48, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-168)
    - CWA Executive Board Meeting; Critique of Executive Board Meeting, Feb 2, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-169)
    - Instant Recall: Sounds That Ring the Bell, Tape 1, May 1, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-170)
    - Instant Recall: Sounds That Ring the Bell, Tape 2, May 1, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-171)
    - Instant Recall: Sounds That Ring the Bell, Tape 3, May 1, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-172)
    - Instant Recall: Sounds That Ring the Bell, Tape 4, May 1, 1978 (Cassette NS26A-173)
    - CWA "Action Line" No. 2-79: CWA and Jimmy Carter, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-174)
    - CWA "Action Line" No. 2-79: CWA and Jimmy Carter, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-175)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: C-1 Mon. Morning; C-2 Watts, Part 1, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-176)
  - Preservation masters, cassettes NS26A 177-193, 201-220 (Box 98)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: C-3 Mon. Evening; Cas-3, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-177)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: Cas 4A; Side B:, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-178)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: Cas 5A, President Carter Introduction; Side B: Cas 5B, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-179)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: Cas 6A; Side B: Cas 6-B, Monday Evening, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-180)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: Cas 7A; Side B: Cas 7B Tuesday, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-181)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: Cas 8A; Side B: Cas 8B, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-182)
    - CWA Convention: Side A: Cas 19A; Side B: Cas 19B, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-183)
    - CWA "Action Line" No. 1-79: Finance Report, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-184)
    - District 8: Watts, Jan 29, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-185)
    - District 8: Watts, Jan 29, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-186)
    - District 9 Conference: President Watts' Comments, Mar 15, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-187)
    - District 9 Conference: President Watts' Comments; Questions & Answers, Mar 15, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-188)
    - CWA Local 1011: "Job Pressures" on WCTC, New Brunswick, NJ, Jun 6, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-189)
    - CWA Executive Board Conference Call, Jun 11, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-190)
    - CWA "Action Line" No. 2-80: Bell South Bargaining Council Press Conference, Jun 11, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-191)
    - CWA "Action Line" No. 2-80: Bell South Bargaining Council Press Conference, Jun 11, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-192)
    - CWA "Action Line" No. 2-80: Bell South Bargaining Council Press Conference, Jun 11, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-193)
    - CWA Press Conference: Bell South Bargaining Council, Jun 11, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-201)
    - CWA "Action Line" No. 4-80: Watts Announces Bell Settlement, Jun 11, 1979 (Cassette NS26A-202)
    - Labor News Conference: Watts, Jan 2, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-203)
    - Bell South Bargaining Council Meeting: Watts' Opening, Mar 11, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-204)
    - Four 60-Second CWA Spots: Maurer, Fleisher & Zon, Inc., Apr 3, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-205)
    - CWA Wed. Morning: Side 1; Side 2: Louis Knecht & Dana Andrews, May 28, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-206)
    - CWA Wed. Morning: Side 3; Side 4: Dana Andrews & Harry Boggs, May 28, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-207)
    - CWA Wed. Morning: Side 5, May 28, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-208)
    - CWA Fri. Morning: Side 1: J. Carroll; Side 2: Lee White, May 30, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-209)
    - CWA Fri. Morning: Sides 3 & 4, May 30, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-210)
    - CWA Fri. Morning: Sides 4 & 5, May 30, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-211)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Mon-1; Side 2: Mon-2, Watts, Jun 16, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-212)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Mon-3; Side 2: Mon-4, Jun 16, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-213)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Mon-5; Side 2: Mon-6, Jun 16, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-214)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Mon-7; Side 2: Mon-8, Charter, Jun 16, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-215)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Tues-11, Jun 17, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-216)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Tues-12; Side 2: Tues-13, Jun 17, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-217)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Tues-14, Jun 17, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-218)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Wed-14; Side 2: Wed-15, Jun 18, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-219)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Wed-16; Side 2: Wed-17, Jun 18, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-220)
  - Preservation masters, cassettes NS26A 221-257 (Box 99)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Wed-17; Side 2: Wed-18, Jun 18, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-221)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Wed-20; Side 2: Wed-21, Jun 18, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-222)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Thurs-22; Side 2: Thurs-23, Jun 19, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-223)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Thurs-24; Side 2: Thurs-25, Jun 19, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-224)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Thurs-26; Side 2: Thurs-27, Jun 19, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-225)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Thurs-28; Side 2: Thurs-29, Jun 19, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-226)
    - CWA "Action Line" No. 3-80: Convention Address, Tape 1, Jun 19, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-227)
    - CWA "Action Line" No. 3-80: Convention Address, Tape 2, Jun 19, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-228)
    - CWA "Action Line" No. 3-80: Convention Address, Tape 2, Jun 19, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-229)
    - CWA "Action Line" No. 3-80: Convention Address, Tape 3, Jun 19, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-230)
    - "A CWA Tribute to George & Mary Miller", Jul 12, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-231)
    - "A CWA Tribute to George & Mary Miller", Jul 12, 1980 (Cassette NS26A-232)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Introduction and President Watts' Address; Side 2: President Watts, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-233)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Monday Morning-1; Side 2: Monday Morning-2, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-234)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Monday, Part 3; Side 2: Monday, Part 4, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-235)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Monday, Part 5; Side 2: Monday, Part 6, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-236)
    - CWA Convention: Side 1: Monday, Part 7; Side 2: Monday, Part 8, 1981 (Cassette NS26A-237)